Finding Aid for the Collection of Material about Japanese American Incarceration LSC.0131
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Miscellaneous, 1929-1956
  - United States. Dept. of the Interior. Division of Budget and Administrative Management. People in Motion: The Postwar Adjustment of the Evacuated Japanese Americans, 1947. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Report on incarceration, public acceptance and attitudes toward resettlement, economic adjustment of incarcerees, forced removal loss and remedial legislation, and social adjustment. Gift of Bradford Smith.
  - Yoshida, Shigeo. In Memoriam: An Address in Honor of the University of Hawaii Varsity Victory Volunteers Who Died In World War II, 1944. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    University of Hawaii Occasional Paper 44, Honolulu. Includes brief history of the Varsity Victory Volunteers, by Margaret Blegen.
  - Poster, "Miles of Hell To Tokyo", 1945. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    World War II recruiting poster published by the War Manpower Commission. Text reads: "Miles of Hell to Tokyo! Work Where You're Needed: Consult Your U.S. Employment Service Office." Illustration by Amos Sewell.